# MARIA HELENA AGUIAR MARTINS

## Front-end Developer

#### Summary

I have been studying HTML, CSS and Javascript since 2020; Vue and ReactJs since 2021. In 2022, I have started working with Typescript. Also. I have been working as frontend developer since April, 2021. Moreover, I have got some knowledge on agile methodologies, such as Kanban and Jira.



+55(11)970809762



lenatinsjs@gmail.com



Mhelena.com.br



https://github.com/HelenaAMartins



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mhelena-martins/

#### **Academic Background**

2022-currently - courses about VUE and ReactJs on Udemy

2020-currently - courses on front end development on Udemy and Alura

2014-2016- Master degree in Literature at Universidade Federal do Ceará

2007-2013- Portuguese and English Language and Literature degree at Universidade Federal do Ceará

## Languages



Portuguese - Native



**English - Advanced** 

#### Skills

- HTML

- VueJs

- CSS

- Kanban

- Sass

- Git | Github | Bitbucket

Javascript

- Directus CMS

- ReactJs

### **Professional Experience**

Magna Sistemas - São Paulo

Front-end Junior

Lacrei - Brasil - remoto

April, 2022 - currently

Front-end Junior Voluntário

Setembro, 2022 - atualmente

**Outroll - Australia** 

Front-end Junior

April, 2021 - September, 2022

Colégio Batista Brasileiro - São Paulo

**English Teacher** 

January, 2020 - April, 2021

Cultura Inglesa - Fortaleza

**English Teacher** 

January, 2014 - December, 2019